我真不敢相信你会这么说
I can't believe you'd actually say that.
我不是咸味先生而是花生先生（卡通人物做的玉米小吃）?
I'd much rather be Mr. Peanut than Mr. Salty.
才怪,咸味先生是个水手
No way. Mr. Salty is a sailor.
他应该是最顽强的点心
He's gotta be the toughest snack there is.
我不知道,你不会想和玉米作对的
I don't know. You don't wanna mess with Cornnuts.
它们简直是疯了
They're crazy.
上帝呀.你们应该看看这个
Oh,my God. You gotta come see this.
有个变态拿着望远镜
There's some creep out there with a telescope.
我真不敢相信他在看我们
I can't believe it. He's looking right at us.
真呕心
Oh,that is so sick.
我感觉被冒犯了
I feel violated.
而且很不爽
And not in a good way.
怎会有人这样?
How can people do that?
你们看,丑陋裸男有双重力鞋
You guys,look. Ugly Naked Guy got gravity boots.
六人行 第1季 第20集 罪恶的牙医
The One With the Evil Orthodontist
几年后学童将会把它奉为…
Years from now,school children will study it...
第一次约会的经典加以研读
...as one of the greatest first dates ever.
-是的 -要我说,当然
-Yeah. -I'll say,yeah.
它太令人无法置信
It was unbelievable.
我们可以完全作自己,无须再玩任何游戏
We could be ourselves. We didn't have to play games.
-你打过电话给她没? -让她知道我喜欢她?你疯了不成
-Have you called her? -She'd know I like her. That's crazy.
伙计.你可真恶心啊
Guys. It's gross.
才第二天,你要我显得多渴望?
It's the next day. How needy do I wanna seem?
-对吧 -对,让她慢慢等吧
-I'm right. Right? -Yeah,let her dangle.
我无法相信我爸妈,强迫我找你们这种男人
I can't believe my parents are pushing me to find one of you people.
快,只管去做
Come on. Just do it.
拿起电话打给她 别摆出一付臭男人的样子(义同睾丸素)
Call her. Stop being so testosterone-y.
对了,旧金山真有这道菜
Which,by the way,is the real San Francisco treat.
-是机器 -她的答录机?
-Her machine. -Answering machine?
不,真有意思,是落叶清扫机
No,interestingly,her leaf blower picked up.
你为何不说话?
So,why didn't you say anything?
不行,上次我留话时
No. Last time I left a spontaneous message...
结果说了“对,的确”
... I ended up using the phrase,"Yes,indeed-io."
看,是瑞秋和贝瑞,不,别一起看
Look,it's Rachel and Barry. Don't everybody look.
怎么了?
What's going on?
-他们只是在讲话 -他是否神情落寞?
-They're just talking. -Does he look upset?
他是否像被告知去死的样子?
Does he look like he was told to shove anything?
没有,而且他正在微笑
No. Actually,he's smiling.
我的老天,不要那样干?
Oh,my God. Don't do that.
怎么啦?怎么啦?怎么啦?
What? What? What?
对街的男人踢了一只鸽子
That man across the street just kicked that pigeon.
这就是法案成为法律的原因
And basically,that's how a bill becomes a law.
看?嗨,瑞秋
See? Hey,Rach.
情况如何?
How'd it go?
你们知道吗,真的,真的好极了
You know,it was actually really great.
他带我到俄罗斯茶室餐厅吃饭
Lunch at the Russian Tea Room.
我点了那种鸡肉 一刺就有奶油喷出来的那种
I had that chicken,where you poke it and butter squirts out.
今天真不是鸟儿的好日子
Not a good day for birds.
然后我们去本多尔公司
Then we went to Bendel's.
我告诉他不要,他还是买了香奈儿给我
And I told him not to,but he got me a bottle of Chanel.
真体贴.是在你跟他说之前还是之后送的
That's nice. Now was that before or after you told him...
叫他别再打电话来,别再送你花,别再来烦你?
...to stop calling,stop sending flowers and to leave you alone?
老实说我没机会开口
Right. Well,we never actually got to that.
能再见到他的感觉真好
It was just so nice to see him again.
感觉是那么自在而熟悉
It was comfortable and it was familiar.
感觉真好
It was just nice.
你已讲了两遍
That's nice twice.
他不是在圣坛前被你甩掉的贝瑞吗?
Isn't this the same Barry who you left at the altar?
你上哪儿去了?
Where have you been?
今天和他在一起感觉不同
It was different with him today.
他今天不像是牙医
He wasn't,like,Orthodontist Guy.
我们玩得很开心,这样有什么不对吗?
I mean,we had fun. Is there anything wrong with that?
是的
Yes
-为什么? -我有我的理由
-Why? -I have my reasons.
那么他订婚的对象…
He's engaged to another woman...
是你以前的好朋友这件事呢?
...who happens to be your ex-best friend?
好吧!我知道这样做很傻
All right. I know it's stupid.
我下午会去找他谈分手
I'll see him this afternoon and put an end to it.
我不疯狂吧?我从未像这样
I'm not crazy,right? I mean,it was never like that.
从未
No,it wasn't.
这儿有个小水槽真好
It was so nice having this little sink here.
还挂着…证书
Then with authority,hang up.
你到底留言吗?
Will you just leave her the message?
好的,这就说
Okay. All right,fine.
丹妮尔,没想到是答录机接的
"Oh,Danielle,I wasn't expecting the machine.
有空请回电
Give me a call when you get a chance.
再见
Bye-bye.
哦,天哪
Oh,God.
你这两小时都在忙这个?
That's what you've been working on for two hours?
我在演练
Hey,I've been honing.
-和盘子有何关系? -我要她以为我在餐厅
-What was with the dishes? -She might think I'm in a restaurant.
我过着不错的生活
I might have a life. Like I haven't been sitting here...
不是只在这儿演练数小时的样子
... honing for the last two hours?
-看,又是那个拿望远镜的人. -哦,我的上帝
-The telescope guy's doing it again. -Oh,my God.
拜托,走开,别再往这儿看
Go away. Stop looking in here.
这下可好,他也挥手了
Great. Now he's waving back.
我们得想办法阻止他
We gotta do something.
早上我逮到他往这儿看 真是令我毛骨悚然,我感觉自己无法办事
I caught him looking into our place. I feel like I can't do stuff.
什么样的事情呀?
What kind of stuff?
成熟点行吗,我不是指性
Will you grow up? I'm not talking about sexy stuff...
我只是光着屁股做饭
...but,like,when I'm cooking naked.
你光着屁股做饭?
You cook naked?
对,烤面包,燕麦,不会溅出来的东西
Yeah,toast,oatmeal. Nothing that spatters.
看我干嘛?我毫不知情
What are you looking at me for? I didn't know that.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
贝瑞,这样不好
I just Oh,Barry,this was not good.
不,好.是非常非常好
No,it was. It was very,very good.
-明蒂呢? -我们干得比明蒂好多了
-What about Mindy? -Way better than Mindy.
不,我是指你和明蒂
I mean,what about you and Mindy?
如果你愿意我就和她分手
If you want,I'll break it off with her.
万万不行,别那样做.别为我那样做
No,don't do that. Not for me.
法伯大夫,巴比来做调整
Dr. Farber,Bobby Rush is here for his adjustment.
谢谢波尼斯
Thanks,Bernice.
我们周末去渡假
Let's go away this weekend.
-贝瑞,这样太… -不,或许我们可以去阿鲁巴
-This is all way too -No,we can go to Aruba.
我在“蜜月”时去过了
When I went there on what would've been our honeymoon...
感觉很棒,你一定会喜欢的
...it was really nice. You would've liked it.
我本来有穿胸罩
I had a bra.
嘿，法伯大夫
Hey,Dr. Farber.
格林小姐,看来一切正常
All right,Miss Greene,everything looks fine.
进步许多
We're starting to see some real progress.
-干嘛? -我十二岁了,我不是傻子
-What? -I'm 1 2,I'm not stupid.
能借用你的电话吗?
Can I use your phone?
我指点你一下,你拿的那支…
For future reference,that thing in your hand...
…也可以当电话使
...can also be used as a phone.
这电话没问题啊
Yes,it's working.
-她为何不回电? -或许她没听到你的留言
-Why isn't she calling? -Maybe she never got your message.
如果愿意你可以打给她的留言机 如果听见许多哔声
Call her machine,and if she has a lot of beeps...
那代表她或许没听见留言
...that means she didn't get her messages yet.
-难道你不认为这样会使我感觉有点 -绝望,渴望,可悲?
-Doesn't that make me seem? -Desperate? Needy? Pathetic?
你显然看过我的私人广告
You obviously saw my personal ad.
哔几声?
How many beeps?
她接的
She answered.
此时你该向她打招呼才对
This is where you'd use that "hello" word.
我不能跟她讲话,她显然听到我的留言
I won't talk to her. She got my message...
而且选择不回电,我既渴望又被人冷落
...and is choosing not to call me. Now I'm needy and snubbed.
我真想念纯渴望的滋味
God,I miss just being needy.
嘿,他表现如何?
So how'd he take it?
事实上,还不错
Pretty well,actually.
你头发上为何有牙线?
How come you have dental floss in your hair?
有吗?
Oh,do l?
-我们在他椅上做爱 -你们在他椅上做爱?
-We ended up having sex in his chair. -You had sex in his chair?
我是否说得太大声?
I said that a little too loudly,didn't l?
你们什么?
You had what?
在他椅上做爱
Sex in his chair.
你到底在想什么?
What...? What were you thinking?
我也不知道,我们仍在乎对方
I don't know. We still care about each other.
我们曾相爱过,就像你和卡萝一样
There's a history there. It's like you and Carol.
不,不像我和卡萝
It's nothing like me and Carol.
如果她说:罗斯我要你躺在这沙发上
If she said to you,"Ross,I want you on this couch...
此时此地,你会怎么回答?
... right here,right now," what would you say?
如果需要我可以过去点
If it helps,I could slide over.
这完全是两回事,这是苹果和桔子
It's a totally different situation. It's apples and oranges.
牙医和女同志,我走了
It's orthodontists and lesbians I gotta go.
-你要上哪儿去? -我就是要走,行吗?
-Where are you going? -I just have to go.
我有自己的人生要过
I have things to do with my life.
我有许多事要做
I have a jam-packed schedule.
被某事耽搁了
And I am late for keeping up with it,okay?
明蒂
Mindy.
你好
How are you?
对,我听说了,恭喜.这真是太好了
Yes,I heard. Congratulations. That is so great.
真的,哦,上帝啊
Really,oh,God
我明天要上班,如果愿意可以到店里
I'm working tomorrow,but if you want,you can come by if you'd like.
太好了
Great.
明天见了
So I'll see you tomorrow.
好的,再见
Okay. Bye.
天呀 天呀 天呀
Oh,God. Oh,God.
明蒂好吗?
So how's Mindy?
她明天想见我,她的语调好诡异,我得打电话给贝瑞
She wants to see me tomorrow. She sounded weird. I gotta call Barry.
是我,我只是,明蒂
It's me. I just Mindy.
明蒂.我想你可能会在那儿
Mindy. No,I figured that's where you'd be.
你这种人都该下地狱
Hell is filled with people like you.
偷窥狂又出现了,蹲下
He's back. The peeper's back.
-蹲下? -蹲下?
-Get down. -Get down?
接着跳舞
And boogie.
我得去上班,接受明蒂的审判
I gotta go and get my eyes scratched out by Mindy.
放轻松,或许她还不知道
She may not even know.
拜托,我们七个月来没联络过 她突然打电话来还会有什么事呢?
I haven't heard from her in seven months,what else is it about?
她曾是我最要好的朋友
She was my best friend.
-我们一起去夏令营,她教我如何亲吻 -是吗?
We went to camp together,she taught me how to kiss....Yeah？
如今我像是成了第三者
Now,you know,I'm,like,the other woman.
-我感觉自己很…-顽皮
-I feel so -Naughty.
-回头见了.-我和你一起出去
-See you later. -I'll walk with you.
她在夏令营时教你亲吻,你穿着制服,还是…
When she taught you to kiss,were you wearing any kind of little uniform?
没事了.
That's fine,yeah.
我要上洗手间,帮我守着电话好吗?
I'm going to the bathroom. Will you watch my phone?
-你何不带进去? -我们还没第二次约会
-Take it with you. -We haven't had a second date...
-她需要听到我尿尿的声音吗? -何不干脆打给她?
-...she needs to hear me pee? -Why don't you call her?
我已留言,不能打给她.我有男性的尊严
I can't. I left a message. I have some pride.
-有吗? -没有
-Do you? -No.
丹妮尔
Danielle,hi.
是我,钱德
It's Chandler.
我很好
I'm fine.
听着…
Listen....
我不知道你是否打过电话给我
I don't know if you tried to call me because...
因为我不小心把电话关了
... I accidentally shut off my phone.
好,太好了
That's fine. That's great. Okay.
她正在讲电话,等一下会回我电话
She's on the other line. She's gonna call me back.
她正在讲电话,等一下会回我电话…
She's on the other line,she's gonna call me back.
-你不想尿了? -这就是我跳舞的原因
-Don't you have to pee? -That's why I'm dancing.
-明蒂. -嗨,你好
-Mindy. -Hey,you.
嗨,你好
Hey,you.
什么事?
So what's up?
我们该坐下来谈
We should really be sitting for this.
当然啦
Sure we should.
我只问一次,我希望你直接回答
I'm gonna ask once,and I want a straight answer.
这好像在问,红色短裤是不是 让我的屁股显得大一些一样
Not like when I asked if those red pants made my ass look big.
我感觉最近有点奇怪
I know things have been weird...
你是我认识最久的朋友,除了萝瑞之外
...but you're my oldest friend,except for Laurie...
她虽已减肥成功
...who's bitter because she lost weight...
但是,脸蛋依然丑陋
...and it turns out,she doesn't have a pretty face.
-我要说了啊. -好的
-Okay,I'm just gonna say it. -Okay.
愿意当我的伴娘吗?
Will you be my maid of honor?
-当然! -太好了
-Of course. -That's so great.
这是,这是,这是
It is. It is. It is.
-这就是你想问我的事? -对,就这样
-That's all you wanted to ask? -That's all.
-怎么了? -不,不只这样
-What? -That's not all.
-当然是的 -也不全是
-Oh,sure it is. -Oh,no,it isn't.
我认为贝瑞有其他的女人
I think Barry's seeing someone in the city.
你怎会这样想?
What would make you think that?
宣布订婚后他就变了样
Since the engagement,he's acted weird.
昨晚他回家时有香奈儿的味道
And then last night,he came home smelling like Chanel.
真的?
Really?
如果这样能让你好过点
If it'll make you feel any better...
我和贝瑞订婚时他也变了样
...when Barry and I got engaged,he was weird too.
瞧,这就是我最担心的
Oh,God. That's what I was afraid of.
什么?你担心什么?
What's what you were afraid of?
贝瑞和你订婚时,我跟他…
When Barry was engaged to you,he and l...
…正在偷偷恋爱
... kind of had a little thing on the side.
-什么? -我知道
-What? -I know,I know.
他向我求婚时,每个人都劝我别接受 他会待你像瑞秋一样
When he proposed,people said,"He'll do to you what he did to Rachel."
如今我只觉得自己好笨
And now I feel so stupid.
明蒂,你真笨
You are so stupid.
我们两人都笨
We are both so stupid.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
是不是熟悉的味?
Smell familiar?
抱歉…
Oh,I'm so sorry.
不,是我抱歉…
Oh,no,me. I am so sorry.
不,我对不起,我抱歉
No,I am sorry. I'm sorry.
哦,我的上帝
Oh,my.
四个字母,圈圈或圆圈
Four letters,"circle or hoop."
-快响（意同圆圈）呀,该死的,快响呀. -谢啦
-Ring,damn it,ring. -Thanks.
-我们的电话坏了. -什么?
-You know our phone's not working? -What?
我从咖啡店打给你没有回音
I called and there was no answer.
我关机了
I turned it off.
上帝他母亲啊,我关机了
Mother of God,I turned it off.
和你告诉她的一样
Just like you told her you did.
我只是指出讽刺的意味来
Just pointing out the irony.
我和对街门房谈过了
I went across the street to the doorman.
他告诉我那偷窥狂的名字,电话能借用吗?
I got the peeper's name. Can I use the phone?
电话能借用吗?
Can I use your phone?
请帮我查辛尼马克斯的电话
The number for a Sidney Marks,please.
热装置?
"Heating device."
散热器
Radiator.
五个字母
Five letters.
“Rdtor.”
"Rdtor."
是辛尼吗?
Yeah,is Sidney there?
辛尼是个女的
Oh,this is? Sidney's a woman.
是女的又怎样?
So she's a woman,so what?
对,那又怎样?
Yeah,so what?
我住在对街.我注意到你拿着望远镜
I live across the street,and I know about your telescope.
而且我很不喜欢你这样
And I don't appreciate it.
我现在就看的见你,嗨
Yeah,I can see you right now. Hello?
如果我要穿着内裤在室内走,我无须感觉…
If I wanna walk around in my underwear,I shouldn't have to feel
谢谢
Thank you.
那不是重点,重点是…
That's not really the point. The point is,that
大部份是宽松的,偶尔
Mostly free-weights,but occasionally
对,我邻居,对,黑褐色头发
Yeah,my neighbor. Yeah,the brunette.
她说你穿绿色套装很好看
She said you looked pretty that day in the green dress.
绿色套装?真的?
The green dress? Really?
对,她说你像英格丽褒曼（美女明星）
She said you looked like lngrid Bergman.
她提到我了吗?
Did she mention me?
她想知道为什么你头上顶块毛巾
She wants to know why you tie the towel around your head.
那是调节器,行不行?
It's a leave-in conditioner,okay?
那是调节器
It's a leave-in conditioner.
-你有时间吗? -当然,当然
-You got a second? -Sure,sure.
进…
Come on...
…来 -亲爱的
-...in. -Hello,sweetheart.
你们来干什么?
What you guys doing here?
我们是来和你分手的
We are here to break up with you.
你们两个?
Both of you?
基本上我们认为你是个大烂人 你该遭到天谴
We think you're a horrible person,and bad things should happen to you.
对不起…我是个白痴
I'm sorry. God,I am so sorry.
我是个懦夫,我无法自拔
I was weak. I couldn't help myself.
不管我做什么都是因为太爱你了
Whatever I did,I only did because I love you so much.
贝瑞,你是指哪一个?
Which one of us are you talking to there?
明蒂
Mindy.
当然是指明蒂.我一直深爱着明蒂
Of course,Mindy. It was always Mindy.
即使我们在你椅上做爱?
When we were having sex in that chair?
我发誓,不论我做什么我都想着你
I swear,whatever I was doing,I was thinking of you.
拜托,第二回合时你根本把她忘得一干二净了
Please. That second time,you couldn't have picked her out of a lineup.
你们做了两次?
You did it twice?
第一次不算,你了解贝瑞的
The first time didn't really count. You know,it was Barry.
明蒂,我亲爱的,再给我一次机会
Honey,sweetheart,look. Just give me another chance.
我们再重新来过,我们再到阿鲁巴去
We'll start over. We'll go back to Aruba.
你和阿鲁巴有什么关系? 你和航空公司有协议吗?
What is it with you and Aruba? Do you have a deal with the airlines?
你怎么说?
What do you say?
法伯大夫,紧急状况
Dr. Farber,we've got an emergency here.
强森被自己的牙套噎到了
Jason Castalano 's choking on his retainer.
拜托,我马上去
Oh,God. I'll be right there,Bernice.
请别离开
Look,please don't go anywhere.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
我们会在这儿的,在这儿恨你
Okay,and we'll be here,hating you.
看见他走出去时满身大汗没?
See how he was sweating when he walked out?
这样吧,我去抓住他那里,然后你跳过去
If I'm hogging the ball,you jump right in there...
…狠狠打他几拳.那感觉一定很爽
...and take some punches. This feels great.
是吗?我还是想嫁给她
I'm pretty sure I'm still gonna marry him.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
明蒂,那家伙是个恶魔
Mindy,the guy is the devil.
是个衣冠禽兽
He is Satan in a smock.
我知道他并不完美
I know he's not perfect.
老实说我还是想当
But the truth is at the end of the day,I still really wanna be...
贝瑞牙医的…
... Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber...
…太太
... D. D.S.
我的天
Oh,God.
希望你能为我高兴
I hope you can find a way to be happy for me.
我希望你还愿意当我的伴娘
And I hope you'll still be my maid of honor.
我希望贝瑞在阿鲁巴不会将你宰了然后吃掉
And I hope Barry doesn't kill you and eat you in Aruba.
你还好吗?
You okay?
真的吗?
Really?
自从我在婚礼上抛下贝瑞
Since I ran out on Barry at the wedding...
我一直在想这决定是否正确
...I've wondered whether I made the right choice.
如今我已得到答案
And now I know.
我真为你高兴
I'm so glad.
大日子
Big day.
告诉你花生先生的穿着比较讲究
I'll give you this: Mr. Peanut is a better dresser.
他有单片眼镜,高帽
He's got the monocle,he's got the top hat....
你知道他是个男同志吗?
Did you know he's gay?
我只想知道你判花生先生出局?
I just wanna clarify this. Are you outing Mr. Peanut?
丹妮尔
Danielle,hi.
各位,她叫丹妮尔,丹妮尔,这是大家
Everybody,this is Danielle. Danielle,everybody.
你为何会出现在这儿?
Why are you here?
我一直打电话给你都一直打错号码
I've been calling,but I had your number wrong.
最后问查号台知道你的号码 却没人接电话
When I got the right one,there was no answer.
我想来看看你是否无恙
So I thought I'd come down here and make sure you were okay.
我没事
I'm okay.
或许我们改天可以见个面
Maybe we could get together later?
这主意不错,我再打给你 或是你打给我
That sounds good. I'll call you. Or you call me,whatever.
一言为定
You got it.
-再见了,各位. -再见
-Bye,everybody. -Bye.
-你会和她. -二次约会
-There you go. -Second date.
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道?
You don't know?
她好像很不错,她大老远来这儿
She seems nice,but her coming all the way here...
只想确定我没事,有这必要吗?
...just to see if I was okay? I mean,how needy is that?